What's that sound?
Wake up, both of you!
Snakes everywhere!
What should we do?
Ja'far, Mystras! Live on for me!
Let's restore our energy by eating this!
Ja'far...
You're... going to eat that?
I've strangled and eaten many of these
during my assassin years.
Let's eat!
Yes!
Take your time, there's plenty of them!
All right, I'm done butchering snakes
for tonight.
Ja'far, are you making progress with that?
Yeah.
I've finished weaving this cloth
made from tree barks.
Wow. I'm impressed, Ja'far.
There's been so many squalls recently.
Let's hope this prevents leakage.
Hey, guys!
Check this out.
A sturdy branch washed ashore,
thanks to the rain the other day.
Great! That's perfect building wood.
All right! Let's repair the house
this afternoon.
But let's have lunch first.
It's all ready to eat.
-Yes!
Yet another day of snake meat...
I'm getting sick of this flavor.
Ja'far.
Here.
Is this rock salt?!
I found it exposed on the cliff behind.
Way to go, Sin!
This one's ready, too.
Go for it, Mystras.
Wow, that looks delicious!
But... wait a minute!
Why are we adapting to this lifestyle?!
This is absurd!
Don't you remember why we're here
in the first place?
The reason why we're here?
-That's right, to survive.
You've got to be kidding me!
This is the Artemyra Kingdom.
We were tossed to the bottom of the valley
because we enraged the queen.
Our goal was to establish diplomacy
with Artemyra.
So, we must return alive
and face the queen again!
I vaguely remember,
now that you've mentioned it.
I remember, too.
Then...!
But I'm pretty comfortable
living here now.
Oh, this one's ready, too.
Thanks.
It's surely a lot more pleasant
than my Sham Lash years.
No!
I realized something by living here.
When I was young,
food was scarce because of the war.
We all helped each other out,
desperately trying to survive each day.
But... I'd forgotten about those times.
I ate excessively well in Reim.
Sleeping in a warm bed
had become the norm.
I was far from being poor.
I've come to realize how I was living
a luxurious and blessed lifestyle.
Living in the bottom of the valley
has humbled me quite a bit.
I'm grateful for the blessings
of the sun and nature.
I pay respects to the animals
who give us their lives.
Yes, this...
is truly what it means "to live."
Sin...
A complete waste of time.
I didn't ask you for enlightenment!
I just want to get out of here
as soon as possible.
-Really?
It's hopeless.
They've forgotten about everything.
Their only concern is how to adapt better.
We're going to end up living
at the bottom of this valley forever.
I won't let that happen.
If I get out of here,
I can see that lady...
If you return from the valley,
let me show you a good time.
No, not that.
I want to fulfill my dream
of traveling the world with Sinbad!
I have to get out of here, no matter what.
Huh?
Holy smokes!
What is it? I want to go back to sleep.
What?!
-Fresh meat?!
A little rotten,
but it's still mouth-watering meat!
It's lamb, too!
How did this get to the bottom
of the valley?!
Mystras, how did you find this?
I found it on the ground
while searching the area last night.
It was already processed when I found it.
So... that means...
we'll have a lamb feast tonight!
Woo-hoo!
No!
Think about it!
This meat has clearly been processed
by human hands!
Don't you think it's suspicious
that it's here?!
It's not a coincidence!
Someone intentionally placed
the fresh meat here.
It could be a clue to our escape!
I want it rare.
That's too risky. It has to be well-done.
Huh?
What's this rock doing here?
It's a precious stone.
You can find a lot of those here.
But I've been ignoring them
since they're inedible.
You're right. We can't even eat it.
Precious stones...
Even precious stones lost to hunger...
These two are far too comfortable
to ever get out of here.
Mystras.
You've led us
into a game-changing situation.
This may be the decisive blow
that will break the deadlock.
Now, show me where you found this meat.
Yes.
Unbelievable.
They weren't here this afternoon.
Yeah.
I wonder who's responsible...
and why.
It's fine meat!
-Gather them all!
-Yes!
Will you quit gathering the meat
and listen for once?!
Of course,
I'm very curious about this meat, too.
But first, we gotta gather them all!
Exactly!
Balalark Meat!
What the heck are you saying?!
Finding out the truth comes first!
This meat might give us a clue
on how to get out of here!
Hey! Give that back!
Don't you dare!
It's those birds of Artemyra!
They're over here, too!
Darn it! That's our meat!
The birds snatched all of them.
No...
That meat could've led us to a way out.
Now it's hopeless.
It's gonna be okay, Mystras.
We've survived up until now.
It seems like fate is on our side.
That's strange.
They're gathering far less stones
than before.
It's the birdies' fault.
So true. They haven't brought us
any meat recently.
No excuses!
But we're trying our best.
So true! You're being tyrannical.
Silence!
Your pay will be commission-based!
So, it will decrease if you can't gather
a sufficient amount!
Oh, no!
If I can't make any money,
my wife will kill me!
Same here, my lady!
Okay, fine! Just focus and keep working!
We'll figure something out on our end.
My lady, you're truly womanly and great!
Women are so reliable!
Hurry!
We gotta gather them all
before the birds take them away again.
Don't leave anything! Let's do this!
He said, "Fate was on our side."
He just wants to eat the meat after all.
I can't trust anyone anymore.
I'm gonna be stuck here forever.
Do not worry, Mystras.
Sin has a plan.
He's the type of man who can...
turn futility into an act of destiny.
So, let's believe in him.
Look at this, guys!
Meat that's not rotten!
I only see a man who wants to eat meat.
It's all in your head, Mystras.
It's all in your head.
This time...
They're gigantic!
They're bigger than ever!
So, what? We still have no way out.
Mystras.
I've been...
waiting for this day to come.
They're the carriers of our destiny!
Good! That should be big enough.
Come back with more precious stones!
Yes, ma'am!
I can't wait! Let's hurry!
Since the meat's bigger,
there's a lot more stones stuck to it.
Hey there.
I'm gonna borrow that cloth.
-Good heavens.
-Please excuse us.
We've been living in nature
for quite some time now.
So, this was why you made us
carve out the meat.
What's this about?
They drop meat into the bottom
of the snake-infested valley
and make the birds pick up
precious stones.
But we started to eat all of that meat.
So, then, they started to think
that a carnivore wandered
into the bottom of the valley
and kept eating all of the meat.
So, they decided to use
massive-sized pieces of meat
that wouldn't get eaten
before the birds came to retrieve them.
Yup. That's exactly what happened.
I wondered why
I didn't see any men in the city.
But they were forced to work here.
Is it possible...
that you're all treated unfairly
by women?
Unfairly?
Oh, of course not!
We're just homemakers.
Only women are allowed to handle animals
in this country.
Women are the ones in charge of labor.
Yes! Instead, men take on the housework
and protect the home.
We take up side jobs like these, too.
Women are busy bees,
working so hard every day.
I totally agree.
The roles of women and men are
completely switched in Artemyra society.
I don't understand it at all.
Let's get to work now.
Looks like they're having
a lot of fun though.
All right!
Sinbad, the world is a vast place.
Indeed.
Now, shall we report to the queen
and show her that we survived?
That's all
for today's governmental affairs.
Have a good night, Your Grace, Mira.
How beautiful is this Metal Vessel
that houses the Djinn?
It's a pity I can't demonstrate its power
since it belongs to another.
But nothing else adorns me better.
Adorns you?
You're wrong.
Your own beauty overpowers
everything around you.
Sinbad?!
I've returned
from the Valley of the Dead...
to see you.
-I wanted to see you.
-Wait.
Yes, I needed to see you.
Because you had my Metal Vessel.
You're so cautious that you use dolls
to take your place in meetings.
I knew that you would keep
the Metal Vessel
where you can keep your eye on it
at all times.
Your Excellency, is something the matter?
Unforgivable.
I'll never forgive you for this, Sinbad.
I'm going to...
make you regret
how you insulted the queen,
Mira Dianus Artemina.
I'll never let a man get away
with such disrespect.
My servant of sternness and fascination.
Take shelter within me.
Transform my whole body
into that of a great magus.
Cerberus!
Let me show you my powers.
Do you think Sinbad is gonna be okay?
Well, he's reckless as always.
But we must save Hinahoho
as soon as possible.
Ja'far!
Look!
Bararaq!
Sinbad and the queen are fighting
with Djinn Equips?
The queen's going to use
a lightning Djinn like Baal?
Our lightning might cancel
each other out.
I won't even feel your attacks.
Then may I show you...
the power of the other Djinn?
As I captured several Dungeons
and subdued various Djinns,
I'm able to switch Djinn Equips
and exercise their power.
My servant of deception and confidence.
Transform my whole body
into that of a great magus.
Djinn Equip Valefor!
Another Djinn Equip?
Do you think that trick will work on me?
What are you waiting for?
If you won't attack...
then I will!
What, is that all you've got?
Garufor Zairu!
GARUFOR ZAIRU
A direct hit!
No.
She's unharmed.
Don't make me laugh.
This is the "power"
of a multiple Dungeon Capturer?
Cerberus is a three-headed Djinn.
One governs ice
and the other governs lightning.
And I, the main body, governs fire.
I subdued the ultimate Djinn
that houses three different elements.
I don't need to switch Djinn Equips.
Possessing only two elements,
you cannot defeat me!
I can't believe that such Djinn exists!
There's no way you can win.
At this rate, Sinbad's gonna...
No, let's have faith in him.
Sin must have a plan.
I'll knock you down to the ground!
Cerbero Hadisa!
CERBERO HADISA
Sinbad!
Well, that was close.
But this is the end!
Cerbero Jairu Ranquesa!
CERBERO JAIRU RANQUESA
Sinbad...
How easy.
Guess you were just like
all the other men,
Sinbad.
Your Excellency, I'm not dead yet.
You... How are you here?
How did he pull this off from that stance?
It's working. Valefor's true powers.
True powers?
Yes.
Valefor manipulates ice and snow,
but that's only part of his true power.
You insolent bastard,
running is all you can do?
But you won't be able to escape this.
Fire, lightning and ice.
The ultimate annihilation magic
that combines all three elements.
I'll turn you into ash!
Maximum magic!
Cerbero Kalb Volquesa!
CERBERO KALB VOLQUESA
Impossible!
You cannot do that, Your Excellency.
You'll end up harming the country
that it's your duty to protect.
How is he able to come up behind me?
I never took my eyes off him.
Bastard!
I refuse to be dictated to by a man!
I'm over here.
What's happening?
My attacks are completely wasted.
It's like fighting someone...
from another dimension.
-The queen's moves...
-Yes.
Valefor's ability is "stagnation."
His power to limit the target's movement
is the true ability of that Djinn Equip.
The hail earlier
was created by solidifying water drops
floating in the air.
He then applied the stagnation power
to the queen herself.
It weakened the queen quite a bit.
But she still has no idea...
This can't be! This is the first time
in my life a man has...
I prefer not to treat women this way.
Garufor Kirestal!
The first man to ever... defeat me.